Spring is here! Spring is here!
WOW!
Well, today
I have to say hello.
I don't remember if YouTube is like that.
Here we go!
Hello! I'm Shirt!
Awww!
I have a date this spring.
I have a date!
I've come to a place!
I'm hungry!
When you think of Nagoya, you think of morning!
I knew it!
I want to have a morning meal
I want to bless you both!
Here we are today! Show me something good!
A bread tiger!
It's Bread Tiger!
Yes, the first bakery in Aichi Prefecture!
Have you guys been here before?
Yes, we have!
Yay!
On the first day, everyone loved the rusks at Pantora!
Yes, the manager,
The manager would get them for us.
Rusks.
I love them and we all eat them.
You actually come to the store. You come with us.
For the first time.
I'd like to try a little bit of all the different breads.
It's so stylish on the outside.
It's so cute.
It's like...
Isn't it like we're in a movie spot?
It's pretty stylish.
It's so cute! So cute!
Pantora has a yellow image, right?
The commercials are crazy too!
All over the place.
Here, look.
There's a pickup locker.
What?
You mean mobile ordering?
Isn't that great?
They can do that? What kind of bakery does this nowadays?
Wow! They make steamed buns!
I want some steamed buns!
Steamed meat buns
Honohon
Steamed meat buns honohon
Amanman
Oh no!
You should come in, for sure.
You're not looking at the bread from the outside, are you?
From the outside, from the bun.
Hey, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
I'm scared.
What do we do?
I don't know.
This is where we started serving breakfast.
It's a totally different place.
They'll come after you order.
Looks good.
It's only 10 servings, and it's only open until 11:00 a.m. every day,
We're full of people, so we've already sold out.
The morning meal.
Delicious.
There are also sandwiches that I bought.
I, curry bread.
Curry bread.
It's bread cream.
So cute!
Isn't this panda a little angry?
He's mad, right here.
Revance.
This bread is only available in real life.
Fried after purchase.
You can do that?
I've never seen it before.
Fry it for me.
It's too tempting. All of it.
All of it.
I want the breaded kind, too.
Delicious.
I'll make it for you.
I can see the verikura!
When you put the beryllium on it...
Yuzu and Totahura
You're acting like a JK!
I bet you love this zone.
Around here.
Side dishes, side dishes.
I like cheese-based side dishes.
She likes cream cheese Dutch.
Dutch.
Curry Bread!
That's the biggest one I've ever had.
Delicious.
Curry bread is the biggest!
Thank you for watching!
Mr. Burdock and Duskeram
Half a loaf? This is...
That's fine.
Chicken and Burdock.
Suddenly we have a dark horse.
I'm sorry, I didn't see that.
I didn't see you there.
It was the first one.
Saba's is here, too.
Looks too good.
Who's that?
Whoever did it did the burdocking.
They're all here.
Here...
Hirayama-san's
They're so cute!
The shape is cute, too!
Hirayama-san thought of it!
It's filled with sakura-an (cherry blossom starch)
Looks delicious!
This one too!
It's from Naito-san's melon bread.
Salmon roe!
Looks delicious!
Strawberry melon bread!
Nai nei-san's amazing!
You've thought of muffins so much!
Nai nei-san is amazing!
I tore up some maple!
Looks so good!
I've never seen that before.
Pulled chili bread!
The walnut cookies look delicious too!
They're so cute!
I think I'll have the walnut cookies.
I'll try that.
Maybe I'll make melon bread.
Ikuta-san's strawberry melon bread!
I'll start with the first one... but it's not that much...
I'll give you a bargain!
Thank you very much.
From now on, sorry, 2,215 yen.
Good, good.
Okay, okay, I'll turn it off.
Thank you very much.
I didn't buy OnimonI didn't buy any onimonium.
I have some free coffee there.
Over here.
Oh, it's in the coffee.
Milk tea.
You see that?
I'll have milk, curry pattachina.
But I'll have a café au lait.
I'll have a café au lait.
Milk tea.
This rusk is ours.
These are the ones we always have.
The usual.
They're delicious.
You want to buy some with us? We buy them together.
Rusks.
And cookies.
They look delicious.
Oh, good!
Rusk and Hollow Hollow
Rusk Hollow Hollow
Wan wan
I've never seen this before.
Milk tea.
You drink this a lot?
I do.
I drink a lot of this.
I drink a lot.
I'm waiting for the commercial.
Anzuki no ah-ha!
It's decided!
Watermelon tarrays!
Watermelon Talay
I'm failing the audition.
I'm not sure I'm ready for watermelon trays right now.
Can I go?
I'm ready.
I can't do it anymore.
Milk tea with apricots.
Isn't it pretty?
Isn't it cute?
You should do it when he's talking.
Cute watermelon tums.
I don't want to smoke again.
Oh, you're not gonna do that? You're gonna have to decide.
Maybe not.
Good morning. Good morning.
Which one do you want first?
Curry buns for sure.
It has sausage buns in it, too.
Sausage bread first.
Good?
Yummy!
The dough is so sticky!
It's delicious... but oh no!
I want to be like Curry Bread.
He said he'd go to Bantora, and I told him I was looking forward to it.
We are good friends, aren't we?
Let's eat a lot of bread
Once he stamped "bread" on my face.
Can I read it out loud?
Sure.
Just enough to stamp my bread.
I'm looking forward to bread.
Fun? Let's have fun. Spring stamped the turtle.
I always use the heart one.
And then the bread... that's everyone's path.
Then you go your own way.
He made a poem with the bread and the illustration.
You have a stamp!
I know, right?
Just standing there is fashionable
I'd like to be told when.
You look like a croissant.
When you do the croissant stamp.
Nice stamp
I want to look like a sausage bread in the spring
Till the day you tell me that this man is a sure thing
Like a loaf of sausage bread
Spring is sausage bread, too!
Oh, really?
I'm sure he'll be around in the spring.
No, no, no, not yet.
Curry buns.
Loved by kids and adults alike.
Isn't that great?
Why curry buns?
Isn't it great? It's like everyone's saying that.
What are you going to do? Nao and Izuki.
Izuki?
But you know what? Saltine bread.
Saltine bread.
There it is.
Salt Bread, Salt Sun
Salty is good.
That's sharp.
It's sweet too.
Spring, what's your type?
Bread.
It's hard to describe.
Stamps. Honoka's stamps.
Let's find out!
My favorite type of bread
Creamy sweet
I've heard of it, but I don't know what it is
I don't know what it is.
Which one?
It's like French bread.
It's cut like this.
Crunchy, kind of sharp looking.
It's kind of shiny.
But when you eat it, it's really sweet.
Shut up!
It's cool to look at.
It's so smooth.
How do they know?
It doesn't sound like it.
But I can't believe you got a voice rose in a bakery.
Now that I've done it.
It's a little bumpy.
The next one will be worse.
Okay, you want half of this?
Yeah, one bite.
I think I just brought out the youngest.
Oh, man.
You always do that.
Looks so good!
Yummy!
Caco salad is delicious!
Yum! Yum!
Is it the tartar sauce?
It's delicious.
It's got a lot of chicken in it.
There's a lot of chicken.
Yum. Yum.
Delicious.
With wine.
Chance.
Boom Boom
Yummy.
What's in it?
Walnuts.
Walnuts and these are cookies.
Walnut cookies.
They're doughy, like mille bread, right?
Yummy.Hey, it's delicious!
It was sweeter as it got to the chokechos.
Yeah, it's like, you know, you can enjoy so many different things in one bite.
Sweet, walnut...
It's amazing.
I mean, all the different flavors, it would've taken me minutes to choose.
You're not usually like that, are you, Dad?
No, I'm not.
Usually.
I usually decide pretty quickly.
I'm the type of person who decides quickly.
But I imagine Yuzuki and Minny are the same.
Decide quickly.
You're hesitating today.
I'm lost today.
I'm on the same level as you are.
There are so many kinds.
What's there?
I don't know.
Halsey, let me see.
May I?
Wow!
This is... I'm so happy to see this.
It's got a huge cross-section. It's got tons of strawberry cream.
Wow!
I thought melon bread was just for the surface.
but it's all the way inside!
I'm so happy!
It's so good!
I can eat more and more.
What are you going to eat it with?
It doesn't even go with anything.
Like cream?
It was a delicious and fun morning.
I'll be back!
There are so many mornings.
I'm done with mornings.
Want to try?
Do you have any recommendations?
We're pretty good ourselves.
We'd love to hear from our fans.
I'd love to hear about it.
Try this place.
This menu is delicious!
I'll recommend it to you.
Take care of one for me!
Let's conquer mornings together!
I'm a fan of Triumph today!
I bought the rusks that I love so much, and I bought them right.
They are really delicious!
First of all, everyone come to Pantora
And I want you to buy some rusks.
Pantola
That's all for now, this is Miki.
See you again.
Bye bye
It's not something bad.
[Subscribe to our channel, please.